[{"answer": "Lunch with her father", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "\"...you just had her..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "No, sir. I just had her", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I. Uh...uh. I had her all day. Tucked her in. At Ten. And she..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "...don't you tell me you were there..", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " ...you lying swine...Don't you tell me you were On Post", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " You had him in his home..", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Where is he...", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The Secret Service", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " What is this sign", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Who called her that...", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Now it's broken.  What's her name...?  WHAT'S HER NAME...  Break his other arm..", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You don't know her name, then who is she...", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "...who was she...", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Who took her", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Who took her", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Was she here", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "The Professor, where's his boat", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "WHERE IS THE FUCKEN BOAT? IS SHE ON THE BOAT..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "...you going to stake out the phone...", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "They can track calls to a payphone", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Not women, Baby. Girls. You got to trust me, I'm the Doctor here...All young. All blonde..", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "In that place. In that place..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What's Maskala...", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, then, you're a philosopher...huh...? How 'bout making me happy tonight..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "...the assault helicopter. You've got no backup, at the house.  You'll be in there, alone, the first few minutes..", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You said", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " I saw the sign...at the that place. In the House", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "...when I dropped the guy. The girl's my friend sign...  She was there. At the that place. The girl was there", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I saw the sign", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I saw the sign", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "\"You saw the sig", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "...then, you tell m", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Why would you want to know?  Listen up, Pal. THEY don't go through the door. WE don't ask why. That's not a COST, it's a Benefit. Because we Got to Travel Light. You wanna lose sleep over it, get over it, or get out.  You wanted to go Through the Looking Glass. How was it? Was it more fun than Miniature Golf...", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Why would I do you a favor", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "My name ain't my friend.", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Back", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "...he was going to come to me that night...after..", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "...his shift", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " The start of a campaig", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Who knows if he knows. His 'people' would let her die in a heartbeat", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Who knows if he knows. His 'people' would let her die in a heartbeat", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " I'm her mother..", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "my frien", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "If that were so, why don't your people go and fetch her...", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "...well, I guess you do have friends in High Places...I mean here you are home, n'all...  And now we're gonna see if you also got all that money that you spoke of.  This here's a Short Subject, if you know what I mean. Of you in that place with an Underage Girl. A PROSTITUE, A MINOR, AND SOMEBODY'S DAUGHTER...  There's another...you know how cheap it is to make a copy...", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I want what you promised me..", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "The last third on exfil, in that place. Me and the Girl. As agreed", "docId": "Spartan.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "What were you going to say...?  ...the Last Third in that place...", "qsentId": 50}]